Interfaith Worker Justice Records 6414
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Stake, Elizabeth Reimbursements etc., 2000 (Box 14, Folder 58)
- Starkey, A Denise, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 59)
- State Farm, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 60)
- Suburban Mailing, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 61)
- UPS, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- US Post Office, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Uptown Bank, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Valenzuela, Claudia, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Vendor List, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Void Checks, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Winch, Jana Reimbursements etc., 2000 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- National Interfaith Committee Wachovia Bank Statements, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- National Interfaith Committee Wachovia Bank Deposits, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Deborah Webber (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Warren Wilcox, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Steven Wilson, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Wilson, Steven Reimbursements, etc., 2000 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Young, Deborah Reimbursements ETC, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Audit, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Reconciliation Report, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Travel - Dayton, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Travel- La Crasse, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- New York SUTA, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- FMCS Reports, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Committee Meeting Costs, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Consumables, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Contractual Costs, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Direct Deposit FMCS, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Financial Status Report, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Health, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- LTD, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Memos, Notes, Interoffice, etc., 2000 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Payroll Verification, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Training, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Transaction Reports, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 31)
- NY Workman's Compensation Policy and Statement, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- Income Tax Withholding, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Printing and distribution costs, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 34)
- Malone, Joan, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Credit Card, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 36)
- Travel - Wausau, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 37)
- NY State Dept. of Labor, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 38)
- Bank Statement (Box 15, Folder 39)
- FMCS Receipts, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 40)
- Telephone, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 41)
- Travel - Retreats, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 42)
- Travel, Sites, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 43)
- FMCS Reimbursements Requests and Forms, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 44)
- Travel, Advisory, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 45)
- Travel Buffalo Chicago, 2000-2001 (Box 15, Folder 46)
- Equipment, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 47)
- Financial and Administrative Grants Manual, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 48)
- FMCS Quarterly Reports official file/copies, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 49)
- FMCS Receipts, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 50)
- National Interfaith Committee for Worker Justice, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 51)
- FMCS Budget/Financial forms, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 52)
- Credit Card, ICMCS expenses, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 53)
- Advisory committee, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 54)
- Travel - NY, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 55)
- Travel - Duluth Minneapolis, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 56)
- Travel - DC, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 57)
- Legal Information Institute, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 58)
- Donnira, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 59)
- GAO, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 60)
- Tammy McCutcheon, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 61)
- Grabowski Thesis, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 62)
- Pilgrims Pride, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 63)
- DOL FOIA, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 64)
- Eggs, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 65)
- Tyson and Perdue, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 66)
- Tyson Subpoena, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 67)
- Barber Foods Court Decision, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 68)
- Tyson Foods FOIA, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 69)
- Commonwealth v. Kimberley, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 70)
- Tyson-Perdue Probe, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- FLSA, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- FLSA 541 Overtime, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- DOL Poultry Settlement, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- DOL FOIA, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- DC - May 9, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- DOL Fact Sheets, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Supreme Court NLRA Decision, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- DOL Nursing Home Compliance Survey, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- DOL, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Poultry Survey, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- DOL - Atlantic City, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- DOL, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- DOL Actions May/June, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- DOL - Developmental Disabilities, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- DOL - Philadelphia, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Sweatshop Taskforce, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Low Income Worker Partnering, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- DOL Training, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- DOL Bulletin Inserts (Box 16, Folder 20)
- DOL Meeting, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Sweatshop Taskforce, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- DOL Michael Kerr, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- DOL Meeting, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- DOL meeting, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- DOL Conference, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Claire Chao Meeting, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- IWJ Voter Guide, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Pulte Report, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- IWJBdStmt End Raids, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Faith Letter to Obama End Raids, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- People of Faith Call Morat. IWJ Stmt, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Congressional Briefing No Match, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 33)
- No Match Event, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 34)
- DHS New Rules - Insecurity (No Match), 2007 (Box 16, Folder 35)
- No Match - IWJ Docs, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 36)
- IWJ Letter on Save, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 37)
- IWJ Pub Comment on E-Verify Mandate for Federal Contractors, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 38)
- Letter to DOL re H-2A rules, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 39)
- Flawed Immigrant Bill Worse, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 40)
- FYWOAS, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 41)
- IWJ Policy Stmt on PSD/HFA, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 42)
- Union Organizing EFCA by KB in FW, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 43)
- Religious Statements Policies - Unions EFCA, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 44)
- IWJ Network Letter on EFCA, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 45)
- EFCA - Virginia, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 46)
- Faith Leaders for Workplace Fairness, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 47)
- EFCA Faith Briefing, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 48)
- EECA Rel ldr sign-on letter, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 49)
- EFCA Talking Points (Box 16, Folder 50)
- Wage Theft Briefing, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 51)
- Wage Theft Hearing, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 52)
- House DOL testimony by Kim Bobo, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 53)
- Wage Theft Hearing, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 54)
- Arkansas, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 55)
- Austin, Texas, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 56)
- Houston, Texas, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 57)
- Mississippi, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 58)
- WC WT Map, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 59)
- Jeffrey Steele Testimony, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 60)
- WT Intro and Definition (Box 16, Folder 61)
- IWJ Recs to Obama Admin/PTT, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 62)
- AR-Little Rock, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 63)
- IWS of Arizona, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 64)
- A Just Minimum Wage, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 65)
- Phoenix Interfaith Committee for Worker Justice, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 66)
- Tucson, AZ, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 67)
- NW Arkansas, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Arkansas - Workers' Center, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Arkansas Little Rock, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- NPJA: Arkansas/gen. info., 2001 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Religious Leaders for Full-Time Justice (Box 17, Folder 5)
- California Statewide Organization, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Los Angeles, CA, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Oakland, CA - EBASE, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Orange County ICWJ, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Palm Springs, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Sacramento, CA, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- San Diego, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- San Diego - Employee Rights Center, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- San Francisco, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- San Jose, CA, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Shreveport, CA, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Soquel, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Watsonville, CA, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- CA - East Bay Oakland/ San Francisco, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- CA - Orange County, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- CA - Sacramento, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- CA - San Jose, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- CA - Los Angeles, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- CA-San Diego, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- CA Trip, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Marin/Here/Background, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- California, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Toolkit for Affordable Housing Advocacy, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- Contra Costa County, CA, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- Los Angeles, CA Clergy and Laity United for Economic Justice, CLUE, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- Marin Co., CA, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 31)
- Monterey Bay, CA Monterey Bay Interfaith Committee for Worker Justice, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 32)
- Oakland, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 33)
- Orange County, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 34)
- Sacramento, CA, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 35)
- San Francisco, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 36)
- San Francisco, CA, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 37)
- San Jose, CA, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 38)
- Oakland, CA, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 39)
- Pueblo Interfaith Council, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 40)
- Colorado, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 41)
- Denver, CO, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 42)
- New Haven, CT, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 43)
- Connecticut, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 44)
- Hartford, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 45)
- Bridgeport/New Haven, CT, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 46)
- Stamford, CT, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 47)
- Waterbury, CT, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 48)
- Delaware Delmarva Poultry Justice Alliance, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 49)
- Miami - So. Florida, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 50)
- Gainesville, FL, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 51)
- Immokalee, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 52)
- Orlando, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 53)
- Florida, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 54)
- St. Petersburg (Box 17, Folder 55)
- Immokalee, FL Religious Leaders Concerned, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 56)
- Orlando, FL, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 57)
- Atlanta, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 58)
- NPJA: Georgia/Literature in Spanish, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 59)
  In Spanish
- Warren's Georgia Work, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 60)
- GA Atlanta, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 61)
- Georgia, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 62)
- Savannah, GA, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 63)
- Hawaii, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Honolulu, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Illinois - Misc., 2005 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Champaign ICWJ, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- DuPage Interfaith Worker Justice, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Chicago Interfaith, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- IL - Chicago, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Champaign - Urbana, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Illinois, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Chicago, IL Interfaith Committee on Worker Issues, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- El Paso, IL, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Peoria, IL, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Springfield, IL, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Calumet Project, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Notre Dame, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- St. Joseph Valley, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Valparaiso, IW, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Indiana, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Central Indiana St. Joseph Valley Project, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Ft. Wayne, IN, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Northwest Indiana Calumet Project, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Indianapolis, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Des Moines, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Iowa, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Des Moines, IA, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Kansas (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Wichita, KS (Box 18, Folder 27)
- Kentucky - JwJ, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- Kentucky, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 29)
- Louisville, KY Worker Rights Outreach Kentucky JwJ, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 30)
- Justice and Peace Lesson Plans, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 31)
- New Orleans, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 32)
- Louisiana, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 33)
- Louisiana - Worker Replacement, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 34)
- Baton Rouge, LA, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 35)
- New Orleans, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 36)
- New Orleans, LA, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 37)
- Maine, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 38)
- Baltimore, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 39)
- Maryland, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 40)
- Montgomery Co., 2000 (Box 18, Folder 41)
- Juno, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 42)
- Salisbury, MD, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 43)
- AFL-CIO Letter to Regina, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 44)
- Boston Interfaith, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 45)
- Springfield, MA Pioneer Valley Project (Box 18, Folder 46)
- MA - Boston, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 47)
- Massachusetts Interfaith Committee for Worker Justice, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 48)
- Amherst, MA, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 49)
- Boston, MA Labor Guild of Boston, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 50)
- Worcester, MA Holy Cross Student Labor Action Committee, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 51)
- Michigan, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 52)
- Detroit, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 53)
- Ann Arbor, MI, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 54)
- Detroit, MI, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 55)
- Grand Rapids, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 56)
- Kalamazoo, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 57)
- Michigan - New, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 58)
- MI - Detroit, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 59)
- Duluth-MN, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 60)
- Rochester, MN, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 61)
- Twin Cities MN, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 62)
- MN - Twin Cities, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 63)
- Minnesota, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 64)
- St. Paul, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 65)
- Mississippi, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 66)
- MS - Mississippi, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 67)
- Kansas City, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Ozarks - Faith Labor Alliance, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- St. Louis/Labor group, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- MO - Kansas City, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- MO - Kansas City, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Missouri, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Springfield, MO, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- St. Louis, MO Labor Religion Committee of the Human Rights Commission, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Montana, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Las Vegas Interfaith Committee, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Nevada Interfaith Council, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- NV - Las Vegas, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- New Jersey, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- New Mexico, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Albany, NY, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Mid-Hudson CEJ, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- New York State, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- New York - Long Island, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Central NY (Syracuse), 2007 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- New York City Interfaith Center, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Rochester, NY, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- New York - Southern Tier, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- NYS Labor Religion Coalition, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- NY - Albany Capital District, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- NY-Buffalo, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- NY-NYC, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- NY - Syracuse, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 27)
- North Carolina - Misc., 2004 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- North Carolina, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 29)
- North Carolina - Western Center, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 30)
- North Carolina - Eastern Center, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 31)
- Greensboro, NC, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 32)
- NPJA: N.C. Gen. Info., 2001 (Box 19, Folder 33)
- NC - Western (Box 19, Folder 34)
  Spanish
- NC - Greensboro, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 35)
- Bismarck, ND UFCW, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 36)
- Ohio Minimum Wage, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 37)
- Cincinnati, Ohio, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 38)
- Xavier University - Cincinnati, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 39)
- Cincinnati ICWJ, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 40)
- Cleveland JwJ, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 41)
- Columbus, OH, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 42)
- Dayton - hospital/clergy, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 43)
- AK Steel - Mansfield, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 44)
- Toledo JwJ, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 45)
- OH - Cincinnati, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 46)
- Oklahoma City, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 47)
- Tulsa, OK, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 48)
- Eugene Springfield ESSN, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 49)
- Portland, OR, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 50)
- Oregon Farm Worker Ministry, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 51)
- Philadelphia ICWJ, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Pittsburgh, PA, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Scranton, PA, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- PA - Philadelphia, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Chicago, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Columbia, SC, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Nashville, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Eastern Tennessee, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Memphis - Mid South, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- TN - Memphis Mid-South, 2011 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Austin Rel-Lab Project/Workers, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Dallas, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- El Paso, TX, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Houston, TX, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- TX - Austin, 2010 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Workers Defense Project Consulting, 2011 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- TX - Houston, 2010 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Salt Lake City, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Vermont, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Virginia, Misc., 2004 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Norfolk, VA, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Richmond, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Seattle, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- DC Employment Justice Center, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- DC Interfaith/Campaigns, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Eily Marlow, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Seminary Correspondence, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- Kimberly Prince, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 28)
- Brent Spodek, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 29)
- Celia Mellinger, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 30)
- Jeffery Crim, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- Dari Rowen, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 32)
- Dennis McCarthy, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 33)
- Gretchen Edwards, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 34)
- Retreat Center (Research Contract), 2002 (Box 20, Folder 35)
- Outreach Delegations, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 36)
- Inquiries, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 37)
- Interviews, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 38)
- West Virginia, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 39)
- Madison - Current, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 40)
- Madison, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 41)
- Madison ICWJ, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 42)
- Milwaukee, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 43)
- WI - Madison, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 44)
- WI - Milwaukee, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 45)
- Board Meeting, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 46)
- Board Covenant Forms, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 47)
- Board meeting - April, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 48)
- December Board Meeting, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 49)
- Directors' Council October Meeting, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 50)
- Department Budgets, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 51)
- Org. Dept. Budget, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 52)
- Fundraising/Org. Dept., 2002 (Box 20, Folder 53)
- Public Policy, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 54)
- Faithful Citz. - Site Coord. Training, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 55)
- OKC, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 56)
- Kansas City, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 57)
- Chicago Interns, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 58)
- Elmira, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 59)
- Syracuse, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 60)
- Twin Cities, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 61)
- Portland, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 62)
- Tulsa, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 63)
- Interfaith Committee On Worker Issues, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Worker Rights Board, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Worker Rights Board, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Study Kit, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Ethical Guidelines, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Barry Buck -2STC, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Chicago Fed. Of Labor AFL-CIO, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Staying Abreast of Labor Issues (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Interfaith Committee On Worker Issues, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Church - Labor Work, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Meeting Dates, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Goals, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Newsletter, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Newsletter Printing, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Interfaith Committee on Worker Issues, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- ICWI - Budget, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- ICWI Budget, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- ICWI - Budget, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- ICWI - Budget, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Internships, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Newspaper Coverage, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Budget/Financial Info, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Africa, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Jobs w/Justice, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Outreach to other cities, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Interfaith Committee on Worker Issues, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Rabbi Marx's Reflection, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Interfaith Committee on Worker Issues, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 28)
- ICWI Steering Committee, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Newlyweds Foods, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 30)
- Sweatshops - Chicago, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 31)
- Frances House, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 32)
- Harper Leather Goods, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 33)
- Caterpillar Executives, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 34)
- St. Bernard's Hospital, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 35)
- Survey Job Quality Requirements - Living Wage, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 36)
- Detroit Newspaper Strike, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 37)
- Brian, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 38)
- Faith and Work, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 39)
- Milwaukee Committee, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 40)
- Roadmaster - Delavin, WI, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 41)
- Pony Express, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 42)
- Brachs, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 43)
- YMCA, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 44)
- BOMA Statement, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 45)
- Briggs Statement Endorsers, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 46)
- Multi-Electric, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 47)
- Opera, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 48)
- Kerr, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 49)
- Homak, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 50)
- Holiday Caroling, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 51)
- ICWI Worship Service, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 52)
- Dixon Meeting, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 53)
- A.D.C, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 54)
- Framburgs, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 55)
- St. Joseph's (Joliet), 1993 (Box 21, Folder 56)
- Lutheran Nursing Home, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 57)
- Free Trade or Fair Trade, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 58)
- ICWI Steering Committee Meeting, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 59)
- St. Joseph's Statement, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 60)
- Provident Hospital, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 61)
- Coalfield, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 62)
- UFW of Washington State, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 63)
- Outside Athenaeum Theatre Co., 1994 (Box 21, Folder 64)
- CA Petty Cash, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 65)
- O'Hare Organizing Campaign (HERE), 1992 (Box 21, Folder 66)
- Social Min Meeting, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Decatur, IL, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- National Farm Worker Ministry, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- One (Box 22, Folder 4)
- ANAR Town Hall, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Campaign for Justice, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- 8th Day Center, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Unitarian - Universalist Indy, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Jobs w/Justice, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- HERE Convention, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Congress of Glenmary Priests, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Chicago Summit for Ethics, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Morganton/Nashville, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Religion News writer Association, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- NYC, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Agricultural Economics, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Highlander, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- DePaul University, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Justice for Workers, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Presby, Louisville, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- LSTC, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Jobs Summit Minneapolis - St. Paul, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Women's Caucus - NCC, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Indianapolis, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- NFWM Dec 6-8 Chapel Hill NC, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 25)
- DC Briefing, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 26)
- SEIN Huntington, WV, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 27)
- Huntington SEIU WVA, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 28)
- USCC meeting, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- WI AFL-CIO Oshkosh, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 30)
- University of Wisconsin, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 31)
- Boston, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 32)
- Harvest of Hope, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 33)
- Printers, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 34)
- Garrett, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 35)
- Global Economics Human Rights, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 36)
- Wonky Women's Lunch, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 37)
- Highlander, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 38)
- WI Impact, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 39)
- Labor Notes, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 40)
- Funders Meeting - Chicago, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 41)
- SEIU, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 42)
- NY State ReRel/Labor, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 43)
- NY State Rel/Labor, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 43)
- LSTC, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 44)
- Staff Retreat, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 45)
- AFL - CIO Lawyers Conference, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 46)
- Action Motown, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 47)
- Social Action Summer Institute, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 48)
- Women in Ministry, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 49)
- Religious Employers Meeting St. Louis, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 50)
- TX State Convention, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 51)
- ARCA, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 52)
- DePaul, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 53)
- TX AFL-CIO, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 54)
- Salvation Army Workshop, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 55)
- NC Summit, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 56)
- Seminary Symposium, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 57)
- Musgrove, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 58)
- Jobs w/Justice Pre Conference, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 59)
- Arca luncheon, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 60)